What the hell is this?
A worn-down castle from the restoration period. Must have been abandoned or forgotten because the location is inconvenient. Or so I assume.
What a sick joke. Those demon bastards are living it up like lords in that thing.
And you're certain that someone from the village was taken here, there is no doubt?
Yes. You have my word. We trapped her up to the castle's tower, but found nothing.
She couldn't have vanished into thin air, idiot. How could you let them ditch you?
I'm truly sorry.
So, this means another woman has disappeared in 24 hours.
Despite the Demon Slayer Corps being on the alert, they still got us.
No one's expecting anything from you chumps.
Hmm. Lucky for us. We may not have gotten here too late after all.
Bastard!
I had a feeling that I should have disposed of them last night.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Bye!
Take that!
You two head back to the village.
From here on, just the wind Hashira and I will proceed.
But, sir...
The two of you will be a hindrance.
Now get out of my sight.
Shinazugawa, something isn't right about this place.
No kidding. I don't like this either.
I've never seen so many demons swarming around like this.
Wind breathing, second form!
Walls, purifying wind!
Serpent breathing, fifth form.
Slithering serpent!
That was close, huh?
I didn't ask for your help!
So powerful!
They're not just any demon slaters.
I may hush you up!
Hey, bastard!
I'm taking her back!
Along with your rotten head!
Step aside!
There's no one in sight to these scum!
Just what are you?
Come, Roses!
Enough!
There's more!
Where the hell are all these things coming from anyway?
Focus on saving the woman.
Leave this to me.
I can handle them on my own.
I was getting bored anyway.
Leave the rest to you!
Serpent breathing, third form.
Third form!
Serpent breathing, third form!
There's more!
Where the hell are all these things coming from anyway?
Focus on saving the woman.
Leave this to me.
I can handle them on my own.
Serpent Breathing, 3rd Form
Coil Choke
You know, even with your friends, you're still not gonna win
Save us some time and die
Wind Breathing, 4th Form
Rising Dust Storm
Really now
If you wanna back that badly
Stop it! What are you doing?
Then take her!
What is this?
Get back here, you bastard!
What the hell is going on?
Hey Shinazugawa, what was that just now?
And where did those demons vanish to?
Hell if I know
You sure I can drop you off at the crossroads ahead?
I...
Miss Canal, thank you for all your hard work.
Welcome back.
Master, I've returned from my mission.
The incident at the Swordsmith Village is as I described the other day.
Mr. Tokito, Ms. Kanroji, also, Kamado and a few others were able to defeat two upper ranks in one night.
Not only that, but Ms. Nezuko appears to have conquered the sun.
Meaning, major developments are just on the horizon for us.
Yes.
It's more than likely that Muzan Kibutsuji is planning to send his demons to abduct Ms. Nezuko.
He wants nothing more than to take possession of the demon who's conquered the sun.
I'll be leaving soon.
An emergency Hashira meeting has been issued by our master, so I'll be heading to the Ubuyashiki mansion.
While I'm gone, I have a favor to ask.
Can you take care of Ms. Nezuko?
I'm counting on you.
Oh, I see.
So they're moving already.
Then is everyone in the village all right?
I don't know enough to say for sure, but they're worried more demons might come at night,
so they've been working to get the place restored and moved.
That makes sense.
It's a miracle that it wasn't worse, seeing as two upper ranks showed up.
And they were both such unbelievable opponents.
The Demon Slayer Corps have a few so-called empty villages built for such occasions,
to move right away if anything happened.
Really?
It just goes to show you how farsighted the master and the others are.
Are you sure you should be gorging yourself like that after being unconscious for seven days?
Sure.
After all, Ms. Konroji always eats plenty.
If you ask me, that one's actually something of an outlier.
It only took three days for Ms. Love and Mr. Mist to fully recover, right?
That's right.
They're amazing.
So you're inching closer to the level, little by little.
Well, if it means you'll get well faster, I guess that's fine.
Yup.
It's a miracle everyone survived.
Yes!
Ooh!
I've been dying to ask you this.
I heard something wild happen to your sister.
Will she be okay?
Uh, yes.
She's been strolling around outside while the sun is out, hasn't she?
Isn't that a big deal?
Like a really big deal?
We're having someone look into it further.
But still, we're not sure if she's more human now.
We're just evolving as a demon.
Is it Lady Kojo who's looking into that?
Nope.
Ms. Tamayo.
Who is Ms. Tamayo?
I told you not to stuck your face like that.
You're still recovering.
Show some restraints.
What a close call.
Now that your sister's conquered the sun,
a lot's going to be happening around here.
All the Demon Slayers have been ordered to go on alert.
And I'm told the Hashira are having an emergency meeting.
Whatever's happening, it has me worried.
Are we the last to show up?
I see we've kept you waiting.
Forgive us.
You needn't worry.
Thank you for taking that mission.
No problem.
Konroji and Tokito, I heard you two battled some upper ranks.
Hmm.
It was intense.
At one point, I truly thought I was done for.
But we all pulled through as a team.
Right, Muichiro?
I wish I could have been there too.
Man, how come I never get to run into any upper ranks?
It's out of our control.
All we can do is leave it to fate.
Konroji and Tokito, physically, how have you been since?
Oh, I'm okay.
Thank you for asking.
Wow, he's really worried about me.
So am I.
Although I haven't fully recovered yet.
Good to hear.
Losing any more Hashira would put the core at risk.
Defeating two upper ranks without losing your lives was noble of you.
Something's different about you two.
And your wounds healed abnormally quickly.
What exactly happened?
Concerning their changes.
I trust the Master will explain everything.
Thank you all for patiently waiting.
Today's Hashira meeting will be conducted by myself as a stand-in for Kaguya Ubuyashiki.
You see, his conditions worsened.
And therefore, Kaguya, the head of our family, can never appear before you again.
I'm sorry.
I know this must be hard.
Understood.
I pray that the Master finds the strength.
The strength to let the light of his life continue burning,
even one day longer.
And I pray that you can stay strong yourself, Lady Amane.
From the bottom of my heart, I want to thank each and every one of you.
I believe that you're already aware of this, but now that a demon who's conquered sunlight has appeared,
it's a given that Musan Kibutsuji will make a frenzied attempt to come after her,
so that he, too, can conquer the sun.
An all-out war of immense scale is approaching us.
But there is hope that was given to us by Lady Kanroji and Lord Tokito.
I'm told that a unique-looking mark appeared on the both of you during your previous battle.
I ask of you, please teach us what you two did to manifest your marks in battle.
Our marks?
During the Sengoku period,
the swordsmen of first breathing who had driven Musan Kibutsuji to the brink of defeat.
What they all shared in common was the mark each of them bore,
a mark similar to demonic patterns.
There are those who are aware of this, having heard through word of mouth.
It's the first time I'm hearing of it.
Why has this been kept secret from us?
Many swordsmen sought to manifest a mark and brooded over not having one appear despite their efforts.
That is why, much of the lore surrounding this mark remained shrouded in mystery.
Perhaps because at the time, it was not seen as vital enough to preserve.
Or perhaps because there was no one to pass it on to, during the many times the Demon Slayer core faced annihilation.
There only remains a single record that describes the manifestation of these marks.
When one person bearing the mark appears, those around him also manifest marks as if resonating with him.
One of the first breathing swordsmen wrote this in his notes.
That's the only clue we have to work with.
However, the first person of our generation to have the mark has appeared.
Shockingly, that person is not a Hashira, but Lord Tanjiro Kamado, the first person to bear the mark.
The only problem is that he himself seemed unable to describe exactly how his mark appeared, so we decided to revisit it another time.
But now, in Lord Tanjiro Kamado's wake, two Hashira have manifested the mark.
Please enlighten us, Lady Kanroji, Lord Tokito.
Oh, right! Lady Amane is so gorgeous!
Well, you see what happened!
My body felt extremely light! Really light! Lighter than usual!
Let's see...
Um...
And then...
Bam!
Throughout my body!
My limbs went bam!
And my mind went pow!
And I remembered my heart pounding like crazy!
And my ears were going ding ding!
And ripple ripple!
Ripple!
I'm so sorry! Forgive me!
I wish I could crawl into a hole right now!
Perhaps I can be of help.
It's not as if I was aware of the mark manifesting.
But when I think about the battle that took place when it did, some things come to mind.
Things that when looking back at it were out of the ordinary.
As long as certain conditions are met, I believe that the mark will appear on everyone.
I'll now explain those conditions and how I met them.
During the previous battle, I was badly poisoned and left unable to move.
I tried to slow down the flow of the poison by using my breathing technique, but before I could,
The boy who tried to save me was about to be killed in front of me, which brought back memories of the past.
And the overwhelming rage I felt made me lose control of my emotions.
I swear at that very moment, my heart rate was over 200.
Furthermore, my body felt like it was on fire.
As for my temperature, I'm certain it was over 102 degrees.
But how could you move in a state like that?
Those conditions are fatal.
Yes, that's correct.
I think that's the point when those who aren't chosen are killed off.
Whether you die or survive in that moment determines whether you get the mark or you become part of the past.
A heart rate over 200 beats a minute.
But your temperature, how do you know it was over 102?
Right.
Well, you see, I remember when I was being treated at Ms. Kochos, I had an abnormally high fever.
In fact, the thermometer reading said 102, like my body heat,
when my mark first manifested itself back during my battle with the upper rank.
Is that right?
That sounds pretty simple if you ask me.
Imagine having such a simple mind that you call this simple.
I envy you.
What did you just say?
Nothing.
So the Hashira's top priority is to awaken these marks, right?
If so, you have my word that we'll figure out how.
Please let the Master know he may rest easy trusting us to do so.
Thank you for your reassurance.
That said, I must relay just one thing regarding any training for manifesting the mark.
What would that be?
I apologize to those whose marks have already appeared, as you have no choice in the matter.
All of those who manifest a mark, eventually, without exception.
I understand.
But if that is the case, then I wonder what will become of me, good lord.
If that's everything from Lady Amane, then excuse me.
Not so fast.
Nobody here excused you.
We still haven't decided what our respective roles will be in manifesting the mark.
I'll let you six discuss that.
It doesn't concern me.
What do you mean it doesn't concern you?
Seems you've forgotten you're also a Hashira.
Or you're bluffing, trying to get a head start on training to manifest the mark.
But you're needed here in the meeting.
Hey, you! Get back here!
Mr. Tomioka, I ask you to explain yourself.
We cannot dismiss this without reason.
It's just I'm not like the rest of you.
I'm not satisfied.
You said the same thing before, Tenyou, Tomioka.
You looking down on us right now?
No fighting, okay?
Let's calm down.
Get back here!
No! No, don't!
Ah!
Yeah!
Sit down.
Let's continue our discussion.
As I have a proposal.
Here.
Wow!
Thank you so much!
Jeez, you sure have an appetite.
Hey, where are those three little ones and your kid sister?
I haven't seen Aoi, either.
Since there aren't any swordsmen in critical condition, they've been outside playing with
Nezuko.
It's thanks to that she's starting to speak little by little.
Oh, I had no idea.
Sounds peaceful.
This rice dumpling is delicious!
Yeah, yeah.
I hear you.
Okay.
Well, enjoy the peace while you can, because that yellow-haired kid should be back soon.
Oh, Mr. Zenitsu!
Does this mean you're back from your mission?
Hey, Kyo!
Safe and sound!
Everyone!
Mr. Zenitsu is back from his mission!
Mr. Zenitsu, thank you for all of your hard work.
Thank you for your hard work!
Did you three gather here just for me?
That's so nice.
You didn't have to do that.
Man, that whole mission, I kept thinking.
I'm gonna die, I'm gonna die, I'm gonna die, I don't wanna die!
But then I thought about how devastated you'd all be if I did die.
So I did it!
You'd be sad if I weren't around, right?
Sorry, not really, no!
But still, we're always glad to see you come back in one piece!
Oh, thanks.
Oh, Mr. Zenitsu, I'm glad to see you're finally back.
Thank you for your hard work.
Miss Howie, you missed me while I was on that mission, didn't you?
You did miss me, right?
I don't know if I'd put it like that.
Welcome home.
You're so cute, I'm gonna die!
Then go right ahead.
Hey, am I going crazy?
Or did you just talk?
For me?
Just for me?
You learn to talk for me?
That makes me so happy!
Oh, please go somewhere else.
Does this mean you and I are getting married?
Get away from her, Greek!
You are a lovely sight to see in the moonlight, but in the sunlight, you're even more beautiful!
Megafizant!
After we get married, I'll make sure you have sushi and eel every day of our married life!
Welcome home, Inosuke!
In...
Inosuke?
Inosuke, welcome home!
Where the hell is that guy?
I think I'll go kill him!
Hey, stop talking like that!
Come to think of it, where's that boarhead kid?
You mean Inosuke?
Huh, he was here this morning.
Your kid's sister sure has been getting schooled by that boarhead, you know?
What's that mean?
Let's check, shall we?
Inosuke!
Big Boss Inosuke!
He's been dead set on making sure she learns his name.
Really?
That's funny, I had no idea.
By the way, do you have any more of these rice dumplings?
You're not done eating?
Hey, Mr. Hageneska!
Have your wounds healed yet?
Oh, good.
Um...
Are you sure you're feeling all right?
Oh, my sword.
Oh, thank you very much.
Mr. Rengoku's sword guard!
Thanks for protecting Kotetsu.
I owe it all to you.
Why don't you come take a seat?
Are you all right?
My blade?
Okay, I'll look at it.
Wow, it's an even deeper shade of black.
That's some high-quality steel there.
So the swordsmen who wielded it must have been exceptionally strong.
The character for destroy.
The swordsmith who first forged this,
meant for it to destroy all demons it came into contact with.
He didn't even engrave his name.
All he left behind was this one character.
I'm told the hierarchy system started after this sword was forged.
And only the Hashira had the words
destroyer of demons engraved on their swords.
I had no idea.
That's incredible.
But I don't remember seeing this character
during my previous battle.
Huh?
I told you.
That's because I only finished the first stage of honing
before you brats took it away and used it against my will.
I hadn't even finished removing the rust yet.
I ought to kill you.
I'm sorry.
My wounds still haven't fully healed.
I can't stop the tears from flowing out.
It hurts so bad I can't take it anymore.
Thanks to the interruptions from that demon in you brats,
I have to start honing it again from scratch.
From scratch!
In terms of severity, the kid's injuries are as bad as yours.
The bones in his body got totally pulverized.
I'm gonna kill you!
Did you hear what I said?
Listen to me, Tanjiro.
You're gonna bring me rice dumplings until the day you die!
You got that?
Rice dumplings!
Yes!
I'll bring them every day!
Thank you for your hard work.
Dead well.
I've heard the rumors about him,
but he sure is a piece of work.
That was actually a mild outburst.
He must be in a lot of pain.
Seriously?
Can you be any noisier over there?
Oh.
Hey there, Genya.
We're done now.
Sorry for that.
He's just...
No, Skate!
You can't just break windows like that!
Are you an idiot?
Lady Kojo's gonna kill you!
Quiet!
He he he!
Coming through!
I wish they just put me in another room.
Training, training, training!
Group strength training is about to start!
Group strength training?
The strongest will gather and train their hardest.
Blah blah blah, something mark!
Huh?
What is that about?
I have no idea!
I see.
As for the Hashira training for the Demon Slayer Corps,
I think we've settled on most of the finer details of our strategy.
Okay.
What about the duration and start date?
I propose we begin in three days' time.
Can we really do that?
It's so soon.
We're racing against time as it is.
And since we have no way of knowing how Muzan Kibutsuji will make his first move,
I'd like for us to be prepared as much as possible.
I agree.
If the demons run rampant again,
it'll be too much for us Hashira alone to handle.
But if we're busy with training,
won't that leave us open to an attack?
Not quite.
As we can assume the demon's top priority right now is capturing Nezuko Kamado.
And ever since the recent attack on the Swordsmith Village,
demon sightings have been dwindling considerably.
If that's the case,
up until now we Hashira have been too busy dealing with demons to train anyone except our own Suguko.
Even if for a short time,
this would be our only chance to provide mentorship to the entire Demon Slayer Corps.
This training is of the utmost importance.
Therefore,
it's vital that we don't waste time.
I propose,
we begin Hashira training in three days.
Save your breath,
Mr. Himejima.
I was sold the moment you started talking.
I too am in agreement.
I have no objections.
Agreed.
Three days is plenty.
Are we certain the training can be handled by just as active Hashira?
I was considering asking the retired Hashira to lend a hand as well.
Are there any objections?
That sounds good to me.
With that decided,
all that's left is Mr. Tomioka.
I finally managed to get back from my mission,
and now we have to train.
Just kill me.
Are you heading there now,
Zenni too?
Unfortunately.
And I heard that we have to train under every Hashira one by one.
What?
Really?
That's great.
There's nothing great about what I just said.
It's awful and hellish.
Whoever thought up this torture,
kill yourself.
Hey,
getting to train with someone who's ranked above you is a privilege,
and a shortcut to getting stronger.
When you take on someone that's better than you,
you can absorb what they teach you and put it into practice.
If you're just gonna spew positive garbage,
and you or I don't know what your friends, you got that?
It's so fine and dandy for you,
because you get to lie in that comfy bed all day when you recover.
But I actually have to go out there and suffer.
Do you know I have to hear?
I'm sorry.
Wait, Zenni too.
Don't you dare talk to me.
But it's important.
You saved me.
Thank you.
During the battle against Upper Four,
when I lost the use of one of my legs,
I remembered what you taught me about the thunder breathing technique.
And because of that,
I was able to behead the demon.
Of course, I couldn't do it nearly as fast as you.
But thank you.
It just goes to show you there are times
when your connections to others can come in handy.
So savor every moment of Hashira training.
After all,
it might lead you to a bright future.
You little chipper idiot.
Don't think flattery is going to put me in a better mood.
Hey, he's happy now.
Thank goodness.
See you, Tanjiro.
Get post soon, okay?
Honestly,
everyone's borderline helpless without me around.
I owe you my life, Zenni too.
Thank you.
Too slow, too slow, too slow!
What the hell are you punks doing?
We're only just getting started here!
Damn!
You're in such miserable shape!
I can't even call it this is running!
I need you to run like you're being chased by a demon!
So get a move on!
Now what's wrong?
Are you speechless?
Who told you to crouch down?
There's no time for taking breaks!
Get up and run!
I'm done.
You can't be serious!
The training from the active Hashira's gonna be much harder than this!
It's nice seeing him like this.
He's much more fired up on the front lines.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
I just hope we can help out a little bit.
They're bound to be famished.
So let's make as many race balls as we can for them.
Hey, Lord Tengen!
Lunch is just about ready!
Great!
Hey!
It's lunchtime, you schmucks!
Can't move.
If I eat, I'm gonna puke!
How pathetic are you?
Lord Tengen, try not to be so angry with them.
Look, I wish I didn't have to.
But if I send them over in this sorry state to the next Hashira, they're gonna blame me for their weakness.
For you, Lord Tengen.
Thanks!
It's me so soup loaded with salt!
This is nothing compared to their training sessions.
Seriously!
Hey, Lord Tengen.
If you're in charge of boosting their stamina,
well then, what will the other Hashira help with?
Well, if I remember right...
First, they'll undergo Tokito's rapid movement training.
That guy has such a deadpan look on his face while being super harsh.
Next up is Kanroji's flexibility training from hell.
And from there, it's on to Igaro.
He'll overhaul their sword skills.
That serpent's one persistent trainer.
Then we have Shinazugawa.
I hear it's called infinite slashing training.
As the name implies, there'll be no end to it.
And finally, Mr. Himejima's muscle amplification training.
They get through that and they'll be superhuman.
The Hashira will too.
After all, they're gonna be taking on an endless stream of rookie swordsmen.
I'm sure they'll end up boosting their own stamina doing it.
Flashy, isn't it?
This training sounds like fun.
I'm a little jealous here.
Good luck.
I'm counting on you all.
And all you got!
At this rate,
my temperature's never gonna go up!
You're too damn weak!
Not bad!
You're almost there!
Let's spread them a little more, okay?
There's no telling where the enemy will attack from next.
Feel it.
Your stance is so full of holes that a demon would have devoured you by now.
In order to maintain the marked state that I've acquired...
Ah, another opening.
Everyone strive to do your best.
This is all for the sake of destroying the demons.
Push through.
For the sake of a master.
For the sake of the demon slayers who've lost their lives.
For the sake of all living people counting on us.
We must see our endeavors through to the end.
We must strive.
What's going on?
Ow!
I'm bleeding!
What's the big idea, huh?
That hurt!
Emergency!
I bear a letter from the master!
Read it without delay!
A letter?
To me?
Are you sure?
Huh.
Let's see.
Huh?
Mr. Tomioka.
He's not taking part in the Hashira training.
Master Kagaya.
It seems the Hashira, preparing for what's to come, have all united and started training the other swordsmen.
Your children are carrying out your will and making sure your hopes live on.
As we speak, they're training their hardest.
All for the sake of your ardent desire to defeat Muzan Kibutsu-ji once and for all.
Amane.
Yes?
Thank you for everything you've done.
Yes.
You're welcome.
Yeah.
Good evening, Miss Tamayo.
It's dangerous, you know, leaving your window open at night like this.
I don't blame you. The moon is truly gorgeous tonight.
Nice to meet you. No need to worry. I'm one of Kaguya Ubyashiki's messengers.
I must say, you really are quite adept at hiding.
So much so that in the time it took to find you, Ubyashiki has become immobile.
If you don't mind sharing, how did you find me?
Merely through human connections.
I was able to identify the former owner of this house that you purchased.
Not only that, but during the day, I kept a watchful eye on Yushiro's whereabouts.
And while I may have received some amount of training, I am a mere crow.
In other words, no one would ever be wary of me.
Please know that I have no intention of harming you. I come in peace.
All right. Then what is it you want with me?
Hmph. I understand you have suspicions. I don't blame you.
I already assumed before meeting you that it would be hard to gain your trust the way Tanjiro has.
Oh well.
What does he intend to do?
Ubyashiki. Is he trying to deceive me somehow?
And Yushiro?
You have my word that Yushiro is safe.
Listen. You can hear his footsteps running towards us.
And now, shall I state my business coming here?
In the Demon Slayer Corps, there is a young girl who is also well-versed in demon physiology.
We'd like you to collaborate with her and look into the changes to Nezuko.
Help us defeat Muzan Kibutsuji. The decision is yours.
We'll be waiting for you at the Ubyashiki Mansion.
You're summoning me, a demon, to the headquarters of the Demon Slayer Corps?
Professor!
You're summoning me, you're voudening me.
You're summoning me, you're summoning me.
Listen. You're open, doctor.
Don't be segundo.
There are no more pressure.
Are youيeryiała?
ность God's wounds
Listen to why I almost liking a certain reason
桃え未来とか 弱さ
それを強さと吐き違っている
憎い 憎い 憎い
隙を隠すほどの
чик ゆだめ 君さえいなければ
揺らいでいる 揺らいでいる 浜のように石をつなぐ
奪っていく 奪っていく 嵐のように心を裂く
永遠の意味 知らぬ君に答えを示す時だ
The end of the day is the end of the day
Within the day is the end of the day
We'll be right back.
Bad boy!
You always stay positive.
And I like that about you, Inosuke.
But there are things that you mustn't do.
Now, hold up your arm so I can tend to your wound.
Don't ever do anything like this again, all right?
Miss Shinobu can be strict whenever she needs to be.
But she's bursting with compassion.
Like back at the Hashira meeting.
Here, Miss Konroji.
Oh, thank you.
You're very welcome, dear.
And that's it for today's Taisho era secret.
Next, episode two, Water Hashira Giyutomioka's Pain.